[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 21, "question": "Ali, what is the situation now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 22, "answer": "Chris, I'm losing you because we've just had a major, major intensification of this storm.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chris"]}, "docId": "130208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 61, "question": "They could get up to three feet, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "TO", "CD", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 62, "answer": "It feels like all of these three feet are falling on us right now, Chris, as we speak.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 94, "question": "Poppy, what is the current condition?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 95, "answer": "Absolutely, it's under a state of emergency.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 126, "question": "Nothing like anchoring your first show in a blizzard, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 127, "answer": "Poppy, thank you very much.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chris"]}, "docId": "130208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 140, "question": "Ashleigh, what's the latest?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "."], "aSentId": 141, "answer": "In fact, it's already happened, Chris.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chris"]}, "docId": "130208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 179, "question": "Help us give us a sense of why this blizzard is a concoction of these two fronts, what it means and where it's moving?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 180, "answer": "One low pressure center, Chris, brought the cold.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "RB", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 239, "question": "How are you managing right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 240, "answer": "I'm a little worried about they say coastal flooding right now, but the mayor, he said, no, it's only going to be two feet.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 244, "question": "When did you expect to move back in?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 245, "answer": "In a matter of a week.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", ",", "CC", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 250, "question": "Are you concerned about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 251, "answer": "Very concerned right now, but so far, it looks good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chris"]}, "docId": "130208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "RB", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 274, "question": "Anybody coming out saying they lost power, or so far so good?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBG", "RP", "VBG", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 275, "answer": "Yes, about six hours ago, even before the snow started coming down, Chris, we were told that 800 customers were without power.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 317, "question": "What do we know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 318, "answer": "Some guns.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "DT", "VBZ", ":", "DT", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 350, "question": "How will that play into how they strategize in this manhunt?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 351, "answer": "Well, in many ways, this is -- this is going to be a traditional fugitive hunt.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "VBG", "JJ", "NNS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 360, "question": "How does that play into making this a difficult task for Mr. Dorner, hopefully?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 361, "answer": "Well, this case obviously is getting national media attention.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Dorner"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 366, "question": "Isn't that a fair assessment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 367, "answer": "WECKER: It is a fair assessment.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 392, "question": "Is there anything in there that fuels this sense of revenge that Dorner says he has?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "NN", "IN", "EX", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 393, "answer": "There's absolutely no basis in reality for his complaints that he was mistreated, that there was any kind of police corruption.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dorner"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 411, "question": "Do you know anything about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 412, "answer": "Yes, I did read about that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 433, "question": "So how do we catch him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 434, "answer": "We do know that he's paranoid.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 474, "question": "Can you hear us?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 475, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Boston"]}, "docId": "130208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 498, "question": "What is the current situation for you there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 499, "answer": "Current situation is we have blowing snow and heavy snow coming in Boston now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "CD", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 511, "question": "What has the response been like?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 512, "answer": "We have a 24 hour service at city hall, 635-4500.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 533, "question": "On the phone with us, Mr. Mayor, what is the latest for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 534, "answer": "Well, it's obviously a very serious storm.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Mayor"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 544, "question": "What reports are you getting so far?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 545, "answer": "You know, I just finished the command staff update, and we have no power outages whatsoever.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New Jersey"]}, "docId": "130208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 553, "question": "Coming out of sandy, to the extent there is any silver lining, what did you learn there that helped prepare for this one?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "IN", "IN", "NN", ",", "TO", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBG", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "EX", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 554, "answer": "Look, I'm really proud of the state of New Jersey as a whole.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 591, "question": "What are you recovering from already?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 592, "answer": "Well, I lost a lot of stuff in my house.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "VBZ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 604, "question": "Is everybody OK so far?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 605, "answer": "Well, everybody has fear, you know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 617, "question": "All the best in the recovery out there, OK?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "DT", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "EX", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 618, "answer": "Thank you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chris"]}, "docId": "130208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 624, "question": "I got you on the phone, pastor?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 625, "answer": "Yes, Chris.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", ",", "NN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 626, "question": "How are you doing this evening?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 627, "answer": "I'm doing well, thank God.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 628, "question": "Let me ask you, how is everybody dealing with the anticipation of what may come with this blizzard?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 629, "answer": "Everybody is really nervous.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 637, "question": "Have people left in preparation for this storm or is everybody still there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "NN", "RB", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 638, "answer": "Some people did evacuate.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 649, "question": "What do you need?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 650, "answer": "The things we need right now are mostly proteins and food.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 675, "question": "What do we know now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 676, "answer": "Chris, it's about halftime.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 684, "question": "Chris?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 685, "answer": "Chad, thank you so much for that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]